

907 Forest Drive, Garner, NC 27529 (919) 921-7562 massengillashlev@icloud.com ashleymassengill.github.io

ashleymassengill.com

Crystal Reports

BACKGROUND

With my past experiences, I have learned where my strengths lie. My goal is to continue to find ways to grow my experience and knowledge in ways that allow me to tap into the creative side of my personality, while always accessing the organized side, to create a product that is the absolute best outcome for everyone involved. I enjoy writing code and turning anyone's design into an interactive product through HTML and CSS.

EDUCATION

i Oct 2016 - Jan 2017 UI Design, The Iron Yard Raleigh, NC 12-week immersive course focusing on interface design and user experience. 700+ hours spent perfecting the art of creating dynamic, interesting, responsive, and user friendly websites. Focused on building foundation skills, clean and efficient coding, and complete shipable product.

East Carolina University

🗓 Aug 2001 - May 2003 🐧 Greenville, NC

WORK HISTORY

Database Manager, RCI, Inc. Apr 2016 - Jul 2016 (\$) Raleigh, NC

- Managed internal tech support including computer hardware, software, phone systems, servers, and website.
- Guided implementation of new AMS through search, demon, contract, setup and testing phases into training and go-live.
- Created and maintained all reporting operations for each department.

Meetings Specialist, RCI, Inc.

i Dec 2010 - Apr 2016

- Managed all event registrations for 10+ attendee events to 1500+ attedee events.
- Created all meeting collateral for international events from general education to conventions and trade shows.
- Produced event based website layouts and coding.

Customer Relations Manager,

i Aug 2007 - Mar 2010

(\$) Raleigh, NC

North Carolina Chamber

- Database management, including ensuring data accuracy.
- Processed all event registrations and assisted in minor logistics.
- Created and maintained all company-wide reporting processes and data analytics.
- Internal IT support in collaboration with external IT team.

STRENGTHS

- ★ Creative Thinking
- **★** Teaching Skills
- ★ Extreme Efficiency
- ★ Analytical Thinking
- ★ Great Eve for Detail
- ★ Organization

TECHNOLOGIES

HTML5 CSS3 SASS **iQuery** Atom GitHub Windows Skeleton Bootstrap iTerm Mac OS Adobe Illustrator Adobe Photoshop Adobe InDesign Microsoft Office Adobe Acrobat Trello

Google Docs

VOLUNTEER HISTORY

Apple iWork

Guest Services NC State Athletics

🗓 Aug 2016 - current (\$) Raleigh, NC

Box Office & Boutique Assistant Carolina Ballet

🗓 Aug 2010 - current Raleigh, NC

Admissions & Ticketing Services USGA Men's & Women's US Open

(\$) Pinehurst, NC 🗓 Jul 2014

Event Assistant SPARKcon

🗓 Sept 2009 \$ Raleigh, NC

INTERESTS









